<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>

<?xml-model href="http://ebeshero.github.io/si-addCheck.sch" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
      <teiHeader>
         <fileDesc>
            <titleStmt>
               <title>Site Index: Additions Template, for Adding and Updating Named Entities in the Digital Mitford Archive</title>
               <author>Digital Mitford Editors</author>
                <editor><persName ref="#lmw">Lisa M. Wilson</persName></editor><!--LMW 2019-05-12-->
               <sponsor>
                  <orgName>Mary Russell Mitford Society: Digital Mitford Project</orgName>
               </sponsor>
               <sponsor>University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg</sponsor>
               <principal>Elisa Beshero-Bondar</principal>
               <respStmt>
                  <resp>Data extraction and compiling by</resp>
                  <persName type="hist" ref="#ebb">Elisa Beshero-Bondar</persName>
               </respStmt>
               <respStmt>
                  <resp>Proofing and corrections by</resp>
                  <persName><!--Add your name here and place an @ref attribute, if you're proofing and correcting existing entries.--></persName><!--LMW:  same thing here:  normally will be you/me/both. Just fill it in that way? -->
               </respStmt>
            </titleStmt>
            <editionStmt>
               <edition> </edition>
            </editionStmt>
            <publicationStmt>
               <authority>Digital Mitford: The Mary Russell Mitford Archive</authority>
               <pubPlace>Greensburg, PA, USA</pubPlace>
               <date>2013</date>
               <availability>
                  <licence>Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported
                     License</licence>
               </availability>
            </publicationStmt>
            <notesStmt>
               <note>Any special notes on this text? (optional)</note>
            </notesStmt>
            <sourceDesc>
               <p>Information on named entities in this file has been extracted from files in the
                  Digital Mitford Archive.</p>
            </sourceDesc>
         </fileDesc>
         <encodingDesc>
            <editorialDecl>
               <p>Describes our editorial practice.</p>
            </editorialDecl>
         </encodingDesc>
      </teiHeader>
      
  <text>
      <body>

         
   <div type="Mitford_Team">
      <listPerson sortKey="Mitford_Team">
         
         <!--LMW: Move to past research assistants: Aymee Woody, Annie Gill, Brooke Stewart, Courtney Younes, Dan Hitt, Jordan Price, John Bawden, Meg Hughes, Olivia Allard, Quinton Reed, Sylvan Baker, Susannah Richey, Shekenko Garrett, Sara Perry  -->
         
         <person xml:id="mgp"> <!--NEW 2019-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Peterson</surname>
               <forename>Martha</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Martha Peterson graduates in 2019 with a B.A. in English: Literature from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Spring and Summer 2019, focusing on transcribing and encoding letters, as well as updating intern training resources. Her interests include feminist theory; the history of sexuality, and cultural and legal responses to sexual assault. She begins a graduate program in law and public policy at the University of Albany in fall 2019.</note>
         </person>
        
         <person xml:id="aol">
            <!--NEW 2018-09-27. Need to add or no? I don't see in SI but I see on web.-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Longmuir</surname>
               <forename>Anne</forename>
               <roleName>Editor</roleName>
               <ptr target="https://www.k-state.edu/english/people/longmuir.html"/><!--If desired, put in link to your professional online profile as the value of the @target attribute, starting with http://-->
            </persName>
            <occupation><affiliation>Kansas State University</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">
               Anne Longmuir is Associate Professor of English at Kansas State University. Anne specializes in Victorian literature and has published more than ten articles and book chapters on Charlotte Bronte, Elizabeth Gaskell, and Wilkie Collins, among others. She also co-edited Victorian Literature: Criticism and Debates (Routledge 2016) with Lee Behlman (Montclair State University). Anne is currently working on a book on the gender politics of John Ruskin's economic theory, which will explore his relationship with several nineteenth-century women writers, including Mary Russell Mitford. Anne is working on Mitford's letters for the Digital Mitford Project. 
            </note>
         </person>
         
         <!--REVISED, replace in SI.-->
         <person xml:id="lmw">
            <persName>
               <surname>Wilson</surname>
               <forename>Lisa</forename>
               <forename>M.</forename>
               <roleName type="lead">Managing Editor</roleName>
               <roleName type="sectionEditor">Bibliography and Correspondence</roleName>
               <roleName>Founding Editor</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York at Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">Lisa M. Wilson is Professor in the Department of English and Communication at SUNY Potsdam, where she has taught since 2005. Her areas of interest include transatlantic Romantic and Victorian era literature, particularly women’s  writing and popular forms such as the Gothic novel and the literary ballad. She is also interested in book history and bibliographical studies, particularly in the study of authorship in the long nineteenth century (1780-1900). She has published in <title level="j">European Romantic Review</title>, <title level="j">Romanticism on the Net</title> (now <title level="j">RaVon</title>), <title level="j">Romantic Circles</title>, <title level="j">Romantic Textualities</title>, and elsewhere. She is currently working on a monograph on Romantic-period authorship and literary celebrity. Her work on Digital Mitford thus far includes editing and coding Mitford’s “Introduction” to her collected <title level="m">Dramatic Works</title> (1854), a critical memoir that recounts the author’s influences and experiences at Covent Garden and Drury Lane in the 1820s and 30s. It also includes researching Mitford’s publication history for the site’s working bibliography, particularly tracking the migration of Mitford’s stories from their first publication to their later reappearances in collections and periodicals. A Founding Editor of Digital Mitford, she and her teams of student research assistants have been at work since 2013 on transcribing, coding, and researching Mitford’s letters from 1819 to the early 1820s and on Mitford's early poems.</note>
         </person>
         
         <person xml:id="kdc"><!--LMW: updated 2017-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Donovan-Condron</surname>
               <forename>Kellie</forename>
               <roleName>Ph.D.</roleName>
               <roleName>Founding Editor</roleName>
               <ptr target="http://www.babson.edu/Academics/faculty/profiles/Pages/Donovan-Condron-Kellie.aspx"/>
            </persName>
            <occupation>Adjunct Lecturer in Arts &amp; Humanities
               <affiliation>Babson College</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">Kellie Donovan-Condron writes primarily about the intersection of urban literature and the Gothic in the Romantic era. Her research interests are an interdisciplinary mix of literature, history, and material culture. Additional areas of particular interest include women's writing, consumerism and consumption in literature, Southern Gothic, and questions about genre and social networking. In the summer of 2013, she was selected to be a summer scholar in the National Endowment for the Humanities seminar "Reassessing Romanticism." She is coding <persName ref="#MRM">Mitford</persName>'s epic poem <title ref="#Blanch">Blanch</title> for the Digital Mitford Archive, and has co-authored with <persName ref="#ebb">Elisa Beshero-Bondar</persName> an article analyzing <persName ref="#MRM">Mitford</persName>'s correspondence network across her lifetime. Previously, she worked on a grant to digitize a collection of 17th- and 18th-century maps and ephemeral materials through the Tufts University Perseus Project.</note>
         </person>
         
         <person xml:id="rnes"> <!--REVISED: updated 2017. I updated her title.-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Nesvet</surname>
               <forename>Rebecca</forename>
               <roleName>Ph.D.</roleName>
               <rolename>Associate Professor of English</rolename>
               
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>University of Wisconsin, Green Bay</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">Rebecca Nesvet's other digital humanities projects include 
               the general editorship of a student-produced edition of James Malcolm Rymer's <ref target="www.salisburysquare.com/TSOP"><title><hi rend="italic">The String of Pearls, or the Barber of Fleet-street</hi></title></ref> (1850), the first complete documentary edition of this source of the legend of <persName>Sweeney Todd</persName>; and  <title><hi rend="italic">Science and Art, a Farce</hi></title>, 
               by Malcolm Rymer (1820), edited by James Malcolm Rymer (1842), in <ref target="http://www.scholarlyediting.org">
                  <hi rend="italic"><title>Scholarly Editing: The Journal of the Association for Documentary Editing</title></hi></ref> 38 (2017). 
               Nesvet's research on James Malcolm Rymer, Romanticism, travel literature, and drama appears in the <title>Keats-Shelley Journal</title><title>Prism(s): 
                  Essays in Romanticism</title>, <title>Notes and Queries</title>, <title>Studies in Travel Writing</title>, <title>Women's Writing</title>, <title>The Review of English Studies</title>, <title>Literature Compass</title>, <title>Shakespearean International 
                     Yearbook</title>, and, in <placeName>Romania</placeName>,><title>American, British, and Canadian Studies</title>.
               She won the <orgName>International Conference on Romanticism</orgName>'s 2012 Lore Metzger Award for the best graduate paper.
            </note>
         </person>
         
         <!--REvised, move to past assistants-->
         <person xml:id="ssc"> <!--REvised, move to past assistants-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Courtney</surname>
               <forename>Shawntel</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Shawntel Courtney graduated in 2018 with a B.A. in English: Writing and a minor in Literature from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Fall 2017 and Spring 2018, focusing on transcribing and encoding letters. Her interests include scholarly editing and British and American fiction of the Romantic period.</note>
         </person>
         
         <person xml:id="cay"> <!--REvised, move to past assistants-->
         <persName>
            <surname>Collins</surname>
            <surname>Younes</surname>
            <forename>Courtney</forename>
            <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
         </persName>
         <occupation>
            <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
         </occupation>
         <note resp="#lmw">Courtney Younes Collins graduated in 2017 with a B.A. in English: Literature from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She is worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Fall 2017, focusing on transcribing and encoding letters. She plans to enter the field of Social Work.</note>
            </person>
         
         <person xml:id="wnb"><!--REvised, move to past assistants-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Barr</surname>
               <forename>William</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation><affiliation>State University of New York at
                  Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">William Barr graduated in 2016 with a B.A. in English Literature, History, and Sociology from the State
               University of New York at Potsdam. He worked on Digital Mitford in Fall 2014.
            </note>
         </person>
         
         
            <person xml:id="jgf"><!--REvised, move to past assistants-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Fish</surname>
               <forename>Julie</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Julie Fish graduated 2017 with a B.A. in English: Literature from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She is worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Spring and Fall 2017. Her interests include bibliographical studies and book history, and she hopes to pursue work in Library and Information Science.</note>
         </person>
            
            <person xml:id="bas"><!--REvised, move to past assistants-->
               <persName>
                  <surname>Stewart</surname>
                  <forename>Brooke</forename>
                  <forename>Ann</forename>
                  <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
               </persName>
               <occupation>Green Scholar, B. A. in English Literature, 2018 <affiliation>University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg</affiliation>
               </occupation>
               <note type="bio">Brooke A. Stewart was a student at the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, where she is pursued a bachelor’s degree in English Literature and a <ref target="http://www.greensburg.pitt.edu/academics/info/digital-studies">Digital Studies Certificate</ref>. She worked a research assistant on the Digital Mitford Project in 2017-2018, focusing on researching, editing, and encoding letters from 1823. Brooke also worked on another digital archive that focuses on Emily Dickinson. Her project, <ref target="http://dickinson16.newtfire.org/"><title level="m">Emily Dickinson</title></ref>, looks closely at Dickinson’s original poem manuscripts and compares them to published versions, which often differ in significant ways from Dickinson’s original work. Brooke is a member of the honor societies Phi Eta Sigma and Sigma Tau
                  Delta, and she was an active participant in Habitat for Humanity on her campus.</note>
         </person>
            
           
         <!--NEW, LMW students: put in past assistants (never got added to SI)-->
            <person xml:id="avm"><!--NEW, LMW students: put in past assistants (never got added to SI)-->
            <persName>
               <surname>McConlogue</surname>
               <forename>Allison</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Allison McConlogue graduated in 2018 with a B.A. in 
               Literature/Writing from the State University of New York at Potsdam and is a member of the English honor society Sigma Tau Delta. She worked as
               a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Spring 2018. She plans to pursue a career in high school teaching in English Language Arts.</note>
         </person>
         
            <person xml:id="adp"><!--NEW, LMW students: put in past assistants (never got added to SI)-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Phoenix</surname>
               <forename>Anaya</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Anaya Phoenix graduates in 2019 with a B.A. in Literature/Writing from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant between Spring 2018 and Spring 2019 focusing on letter transcribing. She plans to pursue a career in high school teaching in English Language Arts.</note>
         </person>
         
            <person xml:id="led"><!--NEW, LMW students: put in past assistants (never got added to SI)-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Dingman</surname>
               <forename>Lindsay</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Lindsay Dingman graduates in 2019 with a B.A. in Literature/Writing and a minor in Communication from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Spring and Fall 2018, focusing on letter encoding, digital image organizing, and bibliography. She will attend graduate school in Library and Information Science at the University at Buffalo.</note>
         </person>
         
            <person xml:id="jbl"><!--NEW, LMW students: put in past assistants (never got added to SI)-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Langer</surname>
               <forename>Jessica</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Jessica Langer graduates in 2019 with a B.A. in Literature/Writing from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She is worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Fall 2019, focusing on letter transcribing. She plans to become a childhood educator.</note>
         </person>
         
            <person xml:id="bal"><!--NEW, LMW students: put in past assistants (never got added to SI)-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Laird</surname>
               <forename>Brytney</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Brytney Laird graduates in 2019 with a B.A. in Literature/Writing and Psychology from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Spring 2019, focusing on letter research and Site Index development. She plans to pursue a career in high school teaching in English Language Arts.</note>
         </person>      
      
            <person xml:id="md"><!--NEW, LMW students: put in past assistants (never got added to SI)-->
         <persName>
            <surname>May</surname>
            <forename>Das</forename>
            <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
         </persName>
         <occupation>
            <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
         </occupation>
         <note resp="#lmw">May Das plans to graduate in 2019 with a B.F.A. in Creative Writing from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Winterim and Spring 2019, focusing on digital image organizing tasks.</note>
      </person>
         
            <person xml:id="ztd"><!--NEW, LMW students: put in past assistants (never got added to SI)-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Deroche</surname>
               <forename>Zakiya</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Zakiya Deroche graduates in 2019 with a B.A. in Communication and a minor in Business from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant in Spring 2019, focusing on digital image organizing tasks. She plans to pursue a career in a Communication-related field.</note>
         </person>
         
            <person xml:id="SM"><!--NEW, LMW students: put in past assistants (never got added to SI)-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Morelli</surname>
               <forename>Sophia</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation>
               <affiliation>State University of New York, Potsdam</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note resp="#lmw">Sophie Morelli graduates in 2019 with a B.A. in Literature/Writing from the State University of New York at Potsdam. She is a member of the English honor society, Sigma Tau Delta. She worked as a Digital Mitford Research Assistant between Summer 2018 and Spring 2019, focusing on letter transcription and encoding, and bibliography. She plans to pursue a career in high school teaching in English Language Arts.</note>
         </person>
         
         <!--LMW: 2017 ERR students, place directly in past assistants, never added to SI-->
         <person xml:id="jcm">
            <persName> <!--LMW: 2017 ERR students, place directly in past assistants, never added to SI-->
               <surname>Mostales</surname>
               <forename>Joshua</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation><affiliation>Robert D. Clark Honors College, University of Oregon</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">Joshua Mostales is an undergraduate student in the Robert D. Clark Honors College at the University of Oregon. He expects to receive his B.S. in Biochemistry in 2019. In summer 2017, he enrolled in Dr. Elizabeth Raisanen's Honors College colloquium on Digital Humanities and subsequently became involved with the Digital Mitford Project, working to transcribe one of Mitford's many letters to Sir William Elford.</note>
         </person>
         
            <person xml:id="lrs"> <!--LMW: 2017 ERR students, place directly in past assistants, never added to SI-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Spillar</surname>
               <forename>Lindsey</forename>
               <forename>R.</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation><affiliation>Robert D. Clark Honors College, University of Oregon</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">Lindsey Spillar expects to graduate from the Robert D. Clark Honors College at the University of Oregon in 2019 with a Bachelor of Science from the Lundquist College of Business with a focus in Finance. She is also completing a minor in Media Studies. In August 2017, she worked with Professor Elizabeth Raisanen in the Honors College for the Digital Mitford Project as a Research Assistant.</note>
         </person>
         
         
            <person xml:id="mbn"> <!--LMW: 2017 ERR students, place directly in past assistants, never added to SI-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Nardoci</surname>
               <forename>Matthew</forename>
               <forename>Blake</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation><affiliation>Robert D. Clark Honors College, University of Oregon</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">Matt Nardoci is a biochemistry major at the University of Oregon and expects to graduate in the summer of 2019. He started working with the Digital Mitford project while enrolled in a Robert D. Clark Honors College class in August of 2017 and has worked on a transcription of one of Mitford's letters.</note>
         </person>
         
            <person xml:id="ms"> <!--LMW: 2017 ERR students, place directly in past assistants, never added to SI-->
           <persName>
               <surname>Scott</surname>
               <forename>Madelyn</forename>
               <forename>N.</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation><affiliation>Robert D. Clark Honors College, University of Oregon</affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">Madelyn N. Scott plans to graduate in 2020 with a B.S. in Chemistry from the Robert D. Clark Honors College at the University of Oregon. Her first encounter with the Digital Mitford Project was in Dr. Raisanen's Digital Humanities course in the summer of 2017. Madelyn was drawn to the technological component the project, which captures the interdisciplinary approach of the digital humanities field. For her final project in the course, Madelyn transcribed and coded Mitford's June 13, 1822 letter to Benjamin Robert Haydon.</note>
         </person>
         
            <person xml:id="sg"> <!--LMW: 2017 ERR students, place directly in past assistants, never added to SI-->
            <persName>
               <surname>Gemelas</surname>
               <forename>Sophia</forename>
               <roleName>Research Assistant</roleName>
            </persName>
            <occupation><affiliation>Robert D. Clark Honors College, University of Oregon></affiliation>
            </occupation>
            <note type="bio">Sophia Gemelas is an undergraduate student in the Robert D. Clark Honors College at the University of Oregon. She became involved with Digital Mitford in Summer 2017 when she enrolled in Dr. Elizabeth Raisanen's Digital Humanities class and coded a Mitford letter as part of her final project.</note>
         </person>
         
      </listPerson>
   </div>

         
      </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
