<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
        <titleStmt>
            <title>Site Index of Named Entities in the Digital Mitford Archive</title>
            <author>Digital Mitford Editors</author>
            <editor>Elisa Beshero-Bondar</editor>
            <sponsor>
                <orgName instant="false" full="yes">Mary Russell Mitford Society: Digital Mitford Project</orgName>
            </sponsor>
            <sponsor>University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg</sponsor>
            <principal>Elisa Beshero-Bondar</principal>
            <respStmt>
                <resp>Data extraction and compiling by</resp>
                <persName ref="#lmw" instant="false" full="yes">Lisa M. Wilson</persName>
                <persName ref="#ebb" instant="false" full="yes">Elisa Beshero-Bondar</persName>
                
            </respStmt>
            <respStmt>
                <resp>Proofing and corrections by</resp>
                <persName instant="false" full="yes">Lisa Wilson</persName>
                <persName instant="false" full="yes">Elisa Beshero-Bondar</persName>
            </respStmt>
        </titleStmt>
        <editionStmt>
            <edition>Site Index for the Digital Mitford project. Date: 2019-05-27T18:14:26.103-04:00. Extracted by Elisa Beshero-Bondar.
                Count of all @xml:ids in the current file: 2089. First digital edition in TEI P5, launched on 19 August 2013.</edition>
        </editionStmt>
        <publicationStmt>
            <authority>Digital Mitford: The Mary Russell Mitford Archive</authority>
            <pubPlace>Greensburg, PA, USA</pubPlace>
            <date instant="false">2013</date>
            <availability default="false">
                <licence>Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported
                    License</licence>
            </availability>
        </publicationStmt>
        <!--         <notesStmt>
            <note>Any special notes on this text? (optional)</note>
         </notesStmt>-->
        <sourceDesc default="false">
            <p part="N">Information on named entities in this file has been extracted from files in the
                Digital Mitford Archive.</p>
        </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <encodingDesc>
        <editorialDecl default="false">
            <p part="N">Describes our editorial practice.</p>
        </editorialDecl>
    </encodingDesc>
    <revisionDesc status="draft">
        <listChange ordered="true">
            <change when="2019-05-27" who="#lmw" status="draft">Updated Site Index with new and revised entries from Charles I, Rienzi, and Finden's Tableaux.</change>
            <change when="2019-05-18" who="#ebb">Updated SI entries from old 2017 lists, updated editing team bios.</change>
            <change when="2019-04-21" who="#ebb" status="draft">Simplified the way we designate genus, species in the plant and animal lists, from rs to name. (Rationale: In TEI, rs is not the right element because it's intended for references that aren't names (like pronouns), and genus/species are names.) </change>
            <change when="2019-04-21" who="#ebb" status="draft">Created this changelog on the SI to better log our descriptions of changes. </change>
            <change when="2019-02-17" who="#ebb" status="draft">Set ODD-generated SI schema to be active on this file; note that editor occupations now flag as errors: we need to change where we encode SI editor home institutions and employment titles.</change>
            <change when="2019-02-17" who="#ebb" status="draft">Modifed the Thomas Noon Talfourd entry so the top material better foregrounds his career and connection to MRM. Added a long-missing Charles Kemble entry, and fleshed out internal tagging on Kemble family entries.</change>
        </listChange>
    </revisionDesc>
</teiHeader>
